[{"question":"Is it unlocked so if im on criclet wireless can i connest it there?","date":"asked on April 7, 2019","answers":[{"answer":"You would need to ask Cricket if they support this model, but yes it is unlocked.","date":"· April 8, 2019","answerer":"GoOverstock"},{"answer":"Fyi for those that don’t know, you can have unlocked phones or at&t phones and they will both work on the cricket network. For reference, I have a iPhone 7 Plus that’s originally at&t with a cricket sim. I’ve been using this device for 2 yrs lol","date":"· March 1, 2020","answerer":"Brit J"},{"answer":"I use total wireless and it worked find,it’s support to be unlocked for all networks","date":"· February 12, 2020","answerer":"Robert"},{"answer":"Yes all unlocked phone that take a sim card will work with Cricket. My son works there.","date":"· April 9, 2020","answerer":"Eva Manicom"},{"answer":"Yes, these work with Cricket via their Bring Your Device setup. You buy a new Cricket SIM card pack and, if applicable, port over your existing Cricket phone number OR get a new Cricket number and line.","date":"· December 7, 2019","answerer":"Mommahunee"},{"answer":"Can this be used in the Philippines with a Globe I'm card? (Filipino phone company)","date":"· May 17, 2020","answerer":"Rdnndn"},{"answer":"did it work with cricket?","date":"· November 17, 2019","answerer":"Julia"},{"answer":"I am not sure","date":"· March 9, 2020","answerer":"Xinman"}]},{"question":"Im a little bit skeptical about buying this phone. Is it worth the money or am I better off going to the apple store and getting the phone by hand?","date":"asked on June 4, 2019","answers":[{"answer":"The unit I received looks as new. You can't tell apart from this and a completely new iPhone from the Apple store. That however, is not ensured. Other reviewers have received units with minor defects, so it truly goes down to luck. Also, the unit I received had a generic cable and charger, not originals and it came in a brown box. If you only need a functional iPhone and save a couple hundred bucks, I'd say go for it. If you have a high standard and expect original accessories, you'll do better at an Apple store.","date":"· June 4, 2019","answerer":"Robert Mancera"},{"answer":"It depends on which vendor you use on Amazon. My store CVE PRIME only use buyers remorse returns. The phones have not been refurbished and are only 30 days used. They have a good amount of Apple Warranty left on them. So buy from CVE PRIME and get just as good as the Apple store but ar a good price with the warranty.","date":"· February 8, 2020","answerer":"Ruben"},{"answer":"The XR Product Red I received was perfect. It might as well been new as far as I could tell, I went over the phone with a magnifying glass and never found a single scratch. Great phone and mine is extremely fast, I’m giving it a “BUY”","date":"· January 17, 2020","answerer":"MWC"},{"answer":"So was I at first but it is a leap of faith..I just got my yesterday and it is flawless..it works with my carrier too so definitely worth the money","date":"· February 12, 2020","answerer":"Robert"},{"answer":"You won’t waste your time, I bought one and I love it","date":"· August 3, 2019","answerer":"Romario"}]},{"question":"Is the screen cracked?","date":"asked on January 12, 2020","answers":[{"answer":"No in perfect condition","date":"· January 13, 2020","answerer":"Michelle"},{"answer":"Mine was not","date":"· January 13, 2020","answerer":"Kindle Customer"}]},{"question":"Will it for Mtn network in Nigeria","date":"asked on June 9, 2019","answers":[{"answer":"It is unlocked. Unlocked does not mean compatible. You still need to confirm if this device is supported by your carrier.","date":"· June 10, 2019","answerer":"GoOverstock"},{"answer":"Yes it will","date":"· March 26, 2020","answerer":"KVNG"}]},{"question":"does it come with a apple charger?","date":"asked on May 29, 2019","answers":[{"answer":"Please read the listing. The first content on the listing talks about the condition and accessories. Amazon Renewed is your trusted destination for pre-owned and refurbished products that are inspected and tested to work and look like new. A Renewed supplier who is Amazon-qualified and performance managed, but not Ap… see more","date":"· May 29, 2019","answerer":"GoOverstock"}]},{"question":"is it a dual sim phone?","date":"asked on September 6, 2019","answers":[{"answer":"Apple finally introduces dual-SIM capabilities on its iPhone XS and XR models, meaning you can now have two different phone numbers associated with a single iPhone. For folks burdened by two phones with one for work and one for personal use, adding support for dual SIM and eSIM on iPhone is welcome news indeed!","date":"· September 6, 2019","answerer":"Nexus Prime"},{"answer":"It has the eSIM option","date":"· September 6, 2019","answerer":"GoOverstock"}]},{"question":"Esta desbloqueado?","date":"asked on August 30, 2019","answers":[{"answer":"So ESTA desbloqueado cuando dice unblocked eso quede dicer","date":"· December 5, 2019","answerer":"elrorro87"},{"answer":"No","date":"· September 1, 2019","answerer":"Ronaldo Cawley"}]},{"question":"Can it work with Nigeria sim","date":"asked on June 7, 2019","answers":[{"answer":"yes","date":"· June 11, 2019","answerer":"Daniel"}]},{"question":"Will this phone work in the UK?","date":"asked on January 9, 2020","answers":[{"answer":"It should work anywhere since it’s unlocked.","date":"· January 11, 2020","answerer":"Clyde…"}]},{"question":"Can you connect it to any carrier?","date":"asked on August 22, 2019","answers":[{"answer":"Outside the US, yes you can.","date":"· August 22, 2019","answerer":"monique sint jago"}]}]